<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">MindMaster</string>

    <string name="draw_over_apps" translatable="false">
        When you grant the \"Draw Over Other Apps\" permission to an app, it will be able to :
        \n1. Display content on top of other apps.
        \n2. Interact with other apps, such as starting or stopping other apps.
    </string>
    <string name="noti_per" translatable="false">
        The \"Notification Access\" permission allows our app to read the current set of notifications,
        including any metadata and attached intents.
        \n\nThis permission can be used by apps to provide
        various features, such as :
        \n1. Displaying a list of all your notifications in a single place.
        \n2. Snoozing or dismissing notifications.
    </string>
    <string name="usage_per" translatable="false">
        The \"Usage Access\" permission allows an app to access data about how other apps
        are being used. This data includes the names of the apps, how much time is spent
        in each app, and when the apps were last used.
        \n\nUsage Access permission can be used
        by apps to provide various features, such as:
        \n1. Displaying a list of all the apps that you have used on a given day or week.
        \n2. Blocking or restricting access to certain apps.
    </string>

    <string name="take_a_break" translatable="false">
        Take a break from your phone \nand focus on things that really matter.
    </string>

    <string name="normal_mode" translatable="false">
        Normal mode will allow you to make changes and white list apps/websites at any time.
    </string>

    <string name="strict_mode" translatable="false">
        Prevents you from changing settings and uninstalling the app.
    </string>

    <string name="take_a_break_whitelist" translatable="false">
        Select the applications you want to access when \'Take a Break\' is blocking you
    </string>

    <string name="usage_limit_ex">e.g. 30 minutes per day</string>

    <string name="launches_ex">e.g. 20 launches per day</string>

    <string name="wait_timer_ex">e.g. block access entirely</string>

    <string name="statistics">View your screen time, launch count &amp; more</string>

    <string name="break_inst" translatable="false">
        1. You won\'t be able to use your phone while the break is enabled. \n
        2. Also, you won\'t be able to receive any calls while the break is underway. \n
        3. Enable stop button to be able to stop the break. \n
        4. Enable call button to be able to make calls. \n
        5. Block notifications to prevent further distractions. \n
    </string>

    <string name="motivational_text">
        The secret of getting ahead is getting started.
    </string>

    <string name="profile_note">
        Note: Schedule - Usage Limit &amp; Number of Launches won\'t work for websites and keywords.
    </string>

    <string name="accessibility_service_description">This app requires this setting to detect the keywords and websites in the browser.</string>
</resources>